Guide to the Rudolf Carnap Papers, 1904-2007 ASP.1974.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Name Index, XXVII.
  - Shimony, Anna Marie (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 2)
  - Shufro, Edma and Salwyn (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Shugg, Roger W. (Box 27, Folder 54, Item 21)
  - Shugg, Roger W. (Box 85, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Shugg, Roger W. (Box 102, Folder 47, Item 1)
  - Shute, Clarence (Box 88, Folder 61, Item 3)
  - Shwayder, David S. (Box 91, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Sikking, A. L. (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Silver, Charles L. (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Silvers, Stuart (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 4)
  - Simmons, John E. (Box 27, Folder 54, Item 4)
  - Simon, Frazer (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Simon, Herbert (Box 85, Folder 57, Item 1)
  - Simon, Herbert (Box 90, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Simpson, Thomas M. (Box 27, Folder 37, Item 1)
  - Singer (Box 89, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Sinnen, Jeanne (Box 89, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Sinzheimer (Box 81, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Sitijnoff, Lars (Box 81, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Skolimowski, Henryk (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Skuhra, B. (Box 85, Folder 24, Item 3)
  - Skuhra, B. (Box 85, Folder 25, Item 4)
  - Sladek, Gertrude (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Sluga, H. D. (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Smelters, Gregory (Box 27, Folder 37, Item 1)
  - Smelters, Gregory (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Smith, Diane (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 1)
  - Smith, James C. (Box 82, Folder 23, Item 3)
  - Smith, Justine (Box 91, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Smith, Lawrence (Box 27, Folder 17, Item 4)
  - Smith, William Warren (Box 27, Folder 57, Item 11)
  - Smith, William Warren (Box 85, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Smith, T. V. (Box 90, Folder 71, Item 1)
  - Smullyan, Arthur (Box 85, Folder 51, Item 1)
  - Smullyan, Arthur (Box 88, Folder 77, Item 2)
  - Smullyan, Arthur (Box 89, Folder 43, Item 1)
  - Smuts, J. C. (Box 85, Folder 62, Item 1)
  - Smow, Edgar (Box 94, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Sobel, Howard J. (Box 88, Folder 68, Item 1)
  - Sobel, Lilla (Box 27, Folder 45, Item 1)
  - Sobler, Benedict (Box 102, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Sobler, Benedict and Raya (Box 102, Folder 35, Item 6)
  - Sobocindki, Boleslav (Box 102, Folder 73, Item 1)
  - Soderbrom, Stan (Box 91, Folder 50, Item 1)
  - Sontag, Frederick (Box 85, Folder 46, Item 2)
  - Solmitz, Robert (Box 21, Folder 69, Item unknown container)
  - Solomon, Cyril (Box 94, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Spangenberg, Berthold (Box 85, Folder 18, Item 2)
  - Spaulding, Albert C. (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Spaulding, Albert C. (Box 91, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Spaulding, Albert C. (Box 91, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Speakman, Anne (Box 85, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Spisani, Fraco (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 3)
  - Springer, Julius (Box 84, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Spitzer, D. D. (Box 85, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Sproul, Robert Gordon (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 5)
  - Staager, Adolf (Box 81, Folder 41, Item 1)
  - Stadtman, Verne A. (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Stakgold, Ivar (Box 91, Folder 12, Item 5)
  - Stanley, W. M. (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Stark, Willa F. (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Stark, Willa F. (Box 88, Folder 80, Item 2)
  - Starsky, Morris J. (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Statera, Gianni (Box 90, Folder 10, Item 5)
  - Staudinger, Else (Box 90, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Stauffer, Virginia (Box 83, Folder 36, Item 1)
  - Steck, Joan (Box 82, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Steck, Joan (Box 89, Folder 36, Item 2)
  - Stegmuller, Wolfgang (Box 27, Folder 59, Item 4)
  - Stegmuller, Wolfgang (Box 80, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Stegmuller, Wolfgang (Box 82, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Stegmuller, Wolfgang (Box 84, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Stegmuller, Wolfgang (Box 90, Folder 11, Item 21)
  - Stegmuller, Wolfgang (Box 90, Folder 12, Item 32)
  - Stegmuller, Wolfgang (Box 107, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Stein, Howard (Box 85, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Stein, Howard (Box 90, Folder 13, Item 15)
  - Stein, Howard (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Stein, Lee (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Steinkraus, Warren E. (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Stemmer, Nathan (Box 27, Folder 17, Item 2)
  - Stemmer, Nathan (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Stenius, Eric (Box 94, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Stern, Beatrice (Box 27, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Stern, Willfred (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 1)
  - Stevenson, Charles L. (Box 102, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Stieger, Hansi (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Stillman, E. Clark (Box 95, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Stinespring, Estelle (Box 85, Folder 9, Item 6)
  - Stöger, Elisabeth (Box 83, Folder 37, Item 7)
  - Stone, Christopher D. (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Stone, Hosmer (Box 90, Folder 37, Item 3)
  - Straatsma, Bradley R. (Box 94, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Strache, Irving (Box 27, Folder 17, Item 2)
  - Stramm, Jean (Box 83, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Strauss, Anna (Box 102, Folder 74, Item 2)
  - Strauss, Martin (Box 102, Folder 74, Item 41)
  - Strauss, Martin (Box 102, Folder 75, Item 13)
  - Stuart, Alan (Box 94, Folder 25, Item 3)
  - Stuart, C. I. J. M. (Box 91, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Stubbs, H. W. (Box 95, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Suhler, Lester (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - Sullivan, Charles A. (Box 85, Folder 45, Item 1)
  - Sullivan, Thomas D. (Box 27, Folder 17, Item 8)
  - Suppes, Patrick (Box 27, Folder 17, Item 3)
  - Suppes, Patrick (Box 82, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Suppes, Patrick (Box 84, Folder 60, Item 1)
  - Suppes, Patrick (Box 90, Folder 58, Item 7)
  - Suppes, Patrick (Box 94, Folder 28, Item 8)
  - Suszko, Roman (Box 90, Folder 14, Item 2)
  - Suyin, Han (Box 94, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Svecstrup, Hans (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 1)
  - Svedberg, The (Box 95, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Svirsky, Leon (Box 85, Folder 5, Item 10)
  - Swinburne, R. G. (Box 85, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Swisher, Sarah (Box 83, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Symcox, Geoffrey (Box 80, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Szczesny, Gerhard (Box 102, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Szekely, D. L. (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Szekely, D. L. (Box 102, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - Sztejnbarg, Dina (Box 81, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Takeda, Hiromichi (Box 27, Folder 18, Item 3)
  - Tarski, Alfred (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 1)
  - Tarski, Alfred (Box 27, Folder 18, Item 5)
  - Tarski, Alfred (Box 85, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Tarski, Alfred (Box 89, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Tarski, Alfred (Box 90, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Tarski, Alfred (Box 90, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Tatsch, C. (Box 28, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Taubes, Jacob (Box 27, Folder 39, Item 1)
  - Taubes, Jacob (Box 88, Folder 26, Item 2)
  - Tauli, Valter (Box 80, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Tauli, Valter (Box 95, Folder 30, Item 5)
  - Taylor, Aileen (Box 83, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Taylor, Richard (Box 90, Folder 13, Item 2)
  - Teller, Paul (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Tennessen, Herman (Box 90, Folder 17, Item 13)
  - Thalheimer, Fred (Box 27, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Theil, Christian J. (Box 27, Folder 39, Item 2)
  - Thitrow, G.J. (Box 80, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Thomas, Rolla M. (Box 83, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - Thompson, Dennis F. (Box 27, Folder 18, Item 2)
  - Thompson, George G. (Box 27, Folder 39, Item 1)
  - Thompson, John (Box 27, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Thompson, Michael R. (Box 27, Folder 39, Item 1)
  - Thomson, Stanley J. (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Thorpe, Harold (Box 21, Folder 65, Item 1)
  - Thost, Hanneliese (Box 90, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Thost, Hanneliese (Box 90, Folder 74, Item 1)
  - Thost, Hanneliese (Box 94, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Thurlow, Charles W. (Box 88, Folder 70, Item 1)
  - Tichy, J. (Box 95, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Tillman, Frank (Box 27, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Timerding (Box 78, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Timberfer, J. (Box 29, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Tintner, Gerhard (Box 78, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Tintner, Gerhard (Box 81, Folder 50, Item 2)
  - Tintner, Gerhard (Box 81, Folder 51, Item 1)
  - Tintner, Gerhard (Box 84, Folder 56, Item 30)
  - Tintner, Gerhard (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Toda, Masanao (Box 85, Folder 57, Item 1)
  - Tolman, R. C. (Box 80, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Tondl, Ladislav (Box 80, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Tondl, Ladislav (Box 90, Folder 18, Item 11)
  - Tondl, Ladislav (Box 102, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Travis, Larry (Box 85, Folder 55, Item 6)
  - Tribus, Myron (Box 85, Folder 57, Item 1)
  - Trovik, Olav (Box 102, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Tucker, A. W. (Box 88, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Tugwell, R. G. (Box 88, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Tunturi, Archie R. (Box 27, Folder 39, Item 2)
  - Turner, Merle B. (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Turner, William W. (Box 94, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Tykociner, J. T. (Box 27, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Tyler, Ralph W. (Box 90, Folder 66, Item 8)
  - Tyndall, Gordon D. (Box 85, Folder 34, Item 17)
  - Uhler, H. S. (Box 95, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Ulmer, Jospeh (Box 27, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Ulmer, Otti (Box 27, Folder 40, Item 2)
  - Underhill, Robert M. (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Ungerer, E. (Box 110, Folder 5, Item 7)
  - Ungersbeck, E. (Box 27, Folder 59, Item 1)
  - Ungersbeck, E. (Box 85, Folder 24, Item 7)
  - Ungersbeck, E. (Box 85, Folder 25, Item 7)
  - Ungersbeck, E. (Box 88, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Valerta (Box 81, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Van Looy (Box 102, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Vasa, Andrea (Box 27, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Vaught, Robert L. (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Vaught, Robert L. (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Veblen (Box 81, Folder 43, Item 1)
  - Verhaar, John W. M. (Box 27, Folder 27, Item 2)
  - Vester, G. (Box 83, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Vetter, Hermann (Box 107, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Villarejo, Don (Box 94, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Vincent, R. H. (Box 84, Folder 59, Item 8)
  - Vogt, Hans (Box 84, Folder 59, Item 3)
  - Vonessen, Irmela and Franz (Box 27, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Vuysje, Davy (Box 27, Folder 17, Item 3)
  - Wagar, E. Warren (Box 27, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Waisnerg, Harold (Box 83, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Waismann, Friedrich (Box 90, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Waismann, Friedrich (Box 102, Folder 76, Item 4)
  - Wakeman, John (Box 91, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Wald (Box 79, Folder 36, Item 7)
  - Wald (Box 110, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Walk, Kurt (Box 84, Folder 59, Item 4)
  - Walker, E. (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 1)
  - Walker Gordon L. (Box 90, Folder 39, Item 3)
  - Walker, Stephen L. (Box 85, Folder 51, Item 1)
  - Walker, Owen (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 3)
  - Wall, Robert E. (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Wallace, John R. (Box 91, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Walter, Erich A. (Box 90, Folder 69, Item 5)
  - Wartofsky, Marx (Box 102, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - Waterman, Alan T. (Box 91, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Waterman, Alan T. (Box 91, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Waterman, Alan T. (Box 91, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Ward, John N. (Box 27, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Watanabe, Michael S. (Box 84, Folder 60, Item 5)
  - Watkins, J. W. N. (Box 27, Folder 47, Item 1)
  - Watkins, J. W. N. (Box 88, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Watson, Walter (Box 27, Folder 41, Item 1)
  - Watson, Walter (Box 89, Folder 43, Item 4)
  - Wavre, R. (Box 81, Folder 44, Item 2)
  - Webb, C. W. (Box 27, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Weihmann, Maximiliano (Box 94, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Weiland, Paula (Box 85, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - Weill, Bronia (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Wein, Hermann (Box 27, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Weingartner, Paul (Box 90, Folder 65, Item 5)
  - Weiss, Lynn (Box 85, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Weitz, Morris (Box 89, Folder 43, Item 3)
  - Weizsacker, Carl Friedrich Von (Box 90, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - Wellman, Harry (Box 85, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Wells, Diane (Box 27, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Wells, Donald A. (Box 88, Folder 64, Item 1)
  - Wells, Donald A. (Box 90, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Wells, Hellen (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Wells, Hellen (Box 85, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Weyl (Box 81, Folder 45, Item 1)
  - Whaley, Gordon W. (Box 85, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Wheaton, Donald (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Wheeler, Harvey (Box 94, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Whiston, Andrew (Box 27, Folder 41, Item 3)
  - Whitaker, Robert (Box 95, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - White, Morton (Box 90, Folder 73, Item 4)
  - Whitehead, Alfred North (Box 81, Folder 39, Item 2)
  - Whitehead, Alfred North (Box 110, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Wicke, J. (Box 80, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Wiebe, Richard (Box 27, Folder 41, Item 12)
  - Weigmann, N. A. (Box 82, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Wienpahl, Paul (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Wienpahl, Paul (Box 85, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - Wilder, Mary (Box 91, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Wilder, Mary (Box 91, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Wilkinson, John (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 5)
  - Williams, Donald (Box 79, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Williams, Donald (Box 84, Folder 63, Item 5)
  - Williams, Thyllis M. (Box 27, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Wilson, Charles Z. (Box 94, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Wilson, Edwin H. (Box 27, Folder 41, Item 1)
  - Wilson, John T. (Box 91, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Wilson, Thomas J. (Box 84, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Wilson, W. Kent (Box 27, Folder 41, Item 5)
  - Winnie, John (Box 90, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Winter, A. J. S. (Box 27, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Winter, A. J. S. (Box 80, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Winter, Eduard (Box 27, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Winter, William (Box 90, Folder 45, Item 1)
  - Winther, Angela (Box 80, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Wisdom, J. O. (Box 84, Folder 45, Item 2)
  - Wisdom, J. O. (Box 90, Folder 23, Item 4)
  - Wittgenstein, Ludwig (Box 102, Folder 77, Item 1)
  - Wittgenstein, Ludwig (Box 102, Folder 78, Item 7)
  - Wittmack, Marcia G. (Box 27, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Wittmack, Marcia G. (Box 85, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Wittmack, Marcia G. (Box 85, Folder 10, Item 6)
  - Wohlgemund, Rudi (Box 90, Folder 52, Item 1)
  - Wong, Lai-Ngau M. (Box 85, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Wood, Ledger (Box 27, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Wood, William A. (Box 84, Folder 56, Item 3)
  - Wood, William A. (Box 85, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Wood, William A. (Box 102, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - Woodger, Jospeh H. (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 11)
  - Woodrow, R. J. (Box 88, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Woolman, Marjorie (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 1)
  - Worsley, S. J. (Box 28, Folder 29, Item 4)
  - Wright, Georg Heinrich Von (Box 21, Folder 74, Item 1)
  - Wright, Georg Heinrich Von (Box 90, Folder 24, Item 5)
  - Wright, Georg Heinrich Von (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Wright, Georg Heinrich Von (Box 21, Folder 64, Item 1)
  - Wundheiler, Alexander (Box 81, Folder 37, Item 1)
  - Yin, Fu-Sheng (Box 27, Folder 21, Item 2)
  - York, Carl M. (Box 82, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - York, Carl M. (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - York, Carl M. (Box 91, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - York, Carl M. (Box 91, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Yost, Robert M. (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Yost, Robert M. (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Yost, Robert M. (Box 85, Folder 39, Item 1)
  - Yost, Robert M. (Box 90, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Yost, Robert M. (Box 91, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - Yost, Robert M. (Box 91, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Young, Carl Haven (Box 90, Folder 37, Item 2)
  - Young, Dr. Charles E. (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 1)
  - Young, Dr. Charles E. (Box 80, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Young, Dr. Charles E. (Box 91, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Young, Francis A. (Box 102, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Young, Johann (Box 81, Folder 43, Item 1)
  - Yourgran, Wolfgang (Box 27, Folder 42, Item 8)
  - Zachary, Robert Y. (Box 82, Folder 12, Item 12)
  - Zachary, Robert Y. (Box 82, Folder 15, Item 2)
  - Zachary, Robert Y. (Box 85, Folder 8, Item 8)
  - Zaverdiwos, B. (Box 27, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Zdenko, Tonkovic (Box 27, Folder 42, Item 2)
  - Zeisel, Hans (Box 27, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Zeltin, Gertrude and Kostia (Box 27, Folder 21, Item 10)
  - Zeltin, Gertrude and Kostia (Box 27, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Zeppelin, Grafin (Box 89, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Zerby, Lewis K. (Box 88, Folder 75, Item 3)
  - Zilsel, Paul R. (Box 27, Folder 21, Item 3)
  - Zimmerman, Robert L. (Box 88, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Zink, Sidney (Box 90, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Zohn, Robert (Box 102, Folder 36, Item 2)
- Annotated Offprints, 1910-1972; XXVIII.
  Scope and Contents
  Carnap organized his collection of offprints of other authors into two alphabetized series which we have arbitrarily designated as "Series A" and "Series B". A third group, made up of offprints found later in archival processing in several locations such as among his books or mixed in with his longer runs of journals, have been artificially collected together as "Series C". Usually, Carnap wrote the name of the author in blue pen in block capital letters on the top left of the offprint and underlined it in red. He also frequently wrote on the top right his signature "Carnap" in script in pencil, with a date, presumably the date he received it. Based on these dates, Series A and Series B seem to have been put together concurrently. See, for example, offprints by Kuroda in Box 74 and 98 which were received on the same date, cover similar topics, and yet are filed into two different series. It is not clear what distinguishes the two series since the dates are largely overlapping, the same authors are represented in both (though not the same publications), and both last over the course of his career both in Chicago and Los Angeles.
  Sub-series 4 is a collection of offprints of Carnap's own publications, organized chronologically, with notes regarding if and how much he annotated them.
  - Annotated Offprints of Other Authors - Series A, 1923-1970; 1
    - Topics - Computers; Information Processing, 1959-1968 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Topics - Biology & Biochem, 1962-1966 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Topics - Parity, Symmetry (Phys), 1966 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Topics - Physics, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Topics - Politics, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Topics - Space, 1960-1968 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Topics - Puzzels & Games, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Achinstein, P, 1963-1969 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Agasi, J; Anscombe, F J, 1951-1968 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Asser; Axinn, S; Ayer, A J; Bachmann, F, 1934-1969 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Bahm, A; Ball, V C; Barcan, R; Bar-Hillel, Y, 1960-1968 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Beckner, M; Behmann, H; Bergman, G; Braithwaite, R, 1958-1959 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Cartwright, R; Castañeda, H; Chernoff; China, 1949-1968 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Chisholm, R; Chomsky, N, 1953-1967 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Church, A; Churchman, C, 1940-1960 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Cohen, P; Cohen, J; Copeland, A, 1941-1966 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Copi, I; Copilowish, I; Corti, W, 1939-1963 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Cox, R; Crawshaw, R; Curry, H, 1946-1968 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Danto, A; Davidson, D, 1956-1968 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Davies, J; Davis, R; Day J; Deming, W; Dewey J; Ducasse C; Dumitriu, A, 1938-1969 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Dürr, K; Earman, J; Edmundson, H; Edwards, W, 1949-1968 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Einstein, A; Elliot, R; Ellis, S, 1957-1967 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Essler, W, 1964-1967 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Farell, B; Feigl, H, 1943-1968 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Fels, E; Feyerabend, P, 1955-1964 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Finetti, B; Firth, R; Fisher, R; Fitch, F, 1948-1967 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Frank, P; Frenkel-Brunswik, E; Fraser, J; Friedman, J; Furth, M; Follesdal, D, 1950-1969 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Gamow, G; Gardner, M; Gellner E; Ghose, A; Gode, A; Gold, E, 1953-1966 (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Good, I, 1951-1968 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Goodman, N, 1946-1968 (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Gorn, S, 1966-1969 (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - Gortari, E; Gregor, A; Grünbaum, A, 1953-1966 (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Halldén, S; Haldane, J; Halmos, P; Hanson, N; Harary, F, 1945-1967 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Harman, G; Harsanyi, J; Hartshorne, C; Hájek, P; Hay, W; Heerden, P, 1961-1968 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Heidegger, Martin; Cassirer, Ernst, 1929-1962 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Helmer, O, 1935-1967 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Hempel, C, 1932-1961 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Henkin, L; Hermes, H, 1938-1965 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Hesse, M; Hillman, D; Hintikka, J, 1955-1968 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Hintikka, J, 1963-1967 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Hirshleifer, J; Hiz, H; Hockin, W; Hodges, J; Hoffman, M, 1950-1967 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Hofstadter, A; Hogben, L; Hohenemser, K; Holton, G; Hook, S; Hosiasson, J, 1930-1969 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Hotelling, H; Hutten, E, 1948-1955 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Jeffery, R, 1956-1967 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Juhos, B, 1953-1966 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Kahn; Kaplan, D; Katz, J, 1961-1968 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Kemeny, J, 1953-1964 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Kemeny, J, 1952-1963 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Kendall, M; Kiesow, H; Kleene, S; Kneale, W; Koestler, A; Koopman, B; Kosok, M; Kraft, V, 1937-1966 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Krauss, P, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Kuhns, J, 1960-1970 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Kuhns, J, 1960-1968 (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Kuroda, S; Kyburg, H, 1956-1969 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Lakatos, I; Lazerowitz, A; Lazerowitz, M; Leach, J, 1962-1969 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Leblanc, H, 1949-1963 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Lehrer, K; Lenzen, V; Leonard, H; Levi, I, 1952-1968 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Lewin, K; Lewis, C; Lewy, C; Linke, P; Lucas, J, 1923-1968 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - MacKay, D; Mann, H; Mannoury, G; March, A, 1951-1957 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Margenau, H; Markovic, M; Marschak, J; Martin, N; Martin, R, 1950-1964 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Martin R, 1963-1964 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Martinet, A; Maruyama, M; Mates, B; Maxwell, G; Mazurkiewucz, S, 1941-1962 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - McGreal, I; McGuigan, F; McKinsey, J; McMillan, E; Meckler, L; Meehl, P, 1940-1969 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Mehlberg, H, 1961-1967 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Mehta, V; Menger, K, 1952-1967 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Meyerhoff, H; Miller, G; Mises, R; Mitrovich; Montague, R, 1947-1967 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Moody, E; Moore, A; Morgenbesser, S; Morris, C, 1956-1966 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Morrison, P; Müller, G; Myhill, J, 1957-1968 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Naess, A; Nagel, E; Neisser, H; Newnham, P; Neyman, J; Novick, M, 1964-1969 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Paradies, F; Pasquinelli, A; Patzig, G; Piatt, D; Planck, M; Polya, G, 1926-1968 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Popper, K, 1947-1968 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Putnam, H, 1954-1967 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Quine, W, 1953-1968 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Rand, A; Reichenbach, H; Reitwiesner, G; Religious; Rescher, N; Resnik, M; Richman, R, 1938-1967 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Richter, H; Robinson, A; Rogers, R, 1954-1965 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Rosenblatt, D; Rothstein, J; Roy, S, 1950-1967 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Rozeboom, W, 1958-1967 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Rubin, H; Ruiz, R; Russell, B; Ruytinx, J; Ryle, G; Rynin, D, 1947-1968 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Salmon, W, 1953-1968 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Santayana; Savage, L, 1951-1967 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Savage, L, 1959-1962 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Schaff, A; Scheer, R; Scheffler, I; Schick, F; Schilpp, P; Schischoff, G; Schlegel, R, 1954-1968 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Schleichert, H, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Schmidt, A; Schoeffler, S; Schoff, E, 1950-1955 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Scholz, H; Schrödinger, E; Schulz, D; Schütte, K; Schultzer, B; Schwabhäuser, W, 1935-1968 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Scott, D; Scriven, M; Seeger, R, 1955-1966 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Seldin, J; Sellars, W, 1957-1969 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Sellars, W, 1953-1963 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Sexl, R; Shannon, C; Sheffler, I, 1950-1968 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Shimony, A, 1963-1968 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Shwayder, D; Simon, H, 1953-1963 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Skyrms, B; Sleigh, R; Smart, J; Smokler, H; Smullyan, R; Solomonoff, R, 1957-1967 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Spector, M; Stace, W; Stachowiak, H; Stahl, G, 1966-1968 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Stegmüller, W, 1958-1967 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Stegmüller, W, 1956-1965 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Stein, H, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Stendahl, G; Stevens, S; Stevenson, C; Strache, I; Strawson, P, 1950-1968 (Box 76, Folder 19)